[
  {
	"front": "carry on",
	"back": "= continue",
	"note": [
	  "Don't stop working. <strong>Carry on</strong>."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "go on",
	"back": "= continue going",
	"note": [
	  ""
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "walk on",
	"back": "= continue walking",
	"note": [
	  ""
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "drive on",
	"back": "= continue driving",
	"note": [
	  "Don't stop here. <strong>Drive on</strong>."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "come on",
	"back": "= be quick",
	"note": [
	  "<strong>Come on!</strong> Everybody is waiting for you."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "get on",
	"back": "= manage<br> (in a job, at school, in an exam etc.)",
	"note": [
	  "How was you exam? How did you <strong>get on</strong>."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "hold on",
	"back": "= wait",
	"note": [
	  "Can you <strong>hold on</strong> a minute? (= can you wait?)"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "take off<br/> took off, taken off",
	"back": "= leave the ground (for plans)",
	"note": [
	  "The plane <strong>took of</strong> 20 minutes late, but arrived on time."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "go off<br/> went off, gone off",
	"back": "= explode (a bomb etc.) or ring (an alarm, an alarm clock etc.)",
	"note": [
	  "A bomb <strong>went off</strong> and caused a lot of damage.",
	  "A car alarm <strong>go off</strong> if somebody tries to break into the car."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "give up",
	"back": "= stop trying",
	"note": [
	  "I know it’s difficult, but don’t <strong>give up</strong>.<br> (= don’t stop trying)"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "grow up",
	"back": "= become an adult",
	"note": [
	  "What does your son want to do <strong>when</strong> he <strong>grows up</strong>?"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "hurry up",
	"back": "= do something more quickly",
	"note": [
	  "<strong>Hurry up</strong>! We haven’t got much time."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "speak up",
	"back": "= speak more loudly",
	"note": [
	  "I can’t hear you. Can you <strong>speak up</strong>, please?"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "wake up",
	"back": "= stop sleeping",
	"note": [
	  "I often <strong>wake up</strong> in the middle of the night."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "wash up",
	"back": "= wash the plates etc. after a meal",
	"note": [
	  "Do you want me to <strong>wash up</strong>?<br> (<em>or</em> … to do the washing-up?)"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "slow down",
	"back": "= go more slowly",
	"note": [
	  "You’re driving too fast. <strong>Slow down</strong>!"
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "break down",
	"back": "= stop working (for cars, machines etc.)",
	"note": [
	  "Sue was very late because her car <strong>broke down</strong>."
	]
  },
  {
	"front": "fall over",
	"back": "= lose your balance",
	"note": [
	  "I <strong>fell over</strong> because my shoes were too big for me."
	]
  }
]